Israel is salting the earth in Gaza, so Palestinians won't be able to drink their water or grow food on their land.
Yet we are seeing American officials stand up and boldly say, well, Israel is doing everything in their power to protect civilian life.
We see Israeli officials stand up and say, we are using surgical precision.
It doesn't matter to you that you're being lied to.
Like, even if you don't care about this, like, it doesn't matter to you that you're just being lied to.
This is deplorable.
And it is 100 percent the example of there being an actual effort to eradicate Gaza.
This is genocide.
And we know this because this is what the United States did to the indigenous people of North America.
They didn't just kill them in violence.
No, they dammed their water sources.
They murdered all the buffalo and the bison.
This is thoughtful.
And this is an effort to say, no, you don't get to live when we want to live here.
And that is slaughter.
And that is savagery.
And don't ever let them tell you that anybody else knows how to do it better than them.
You're welcome.